Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records 1925-1967
Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.)
32 linear feet
2011121 Br 2
Summer camp for boys located on Burt lake near Petoskey, Michigan. Records of the camp include medical and other personal information about the campers, the camp counselors, and the other staff members. These files are closed for 100 years from the date of creation.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records came from the Ann Arbor YMCA (donor no. 3698 ) in June 2011
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is closed to research for 100 years from the date of creation.
The site that is now Camp Al-Gon-Quian was originally a farm on Burt Lake in Northern Michigan, just east of Petoskey. In 1925, Herbert H. Twining purchased the land with the intent to start a summer camp. Twining was a University of Michigan graduate (1923), who initially wanted to be a medical doctor. However, an eye injury as a child prevented this and instead Twining pursued a profession that he found parallel: He dedicated his life's work to establishing Camp Al-Gon-Quian as a private boys' camp on the leading edge of camp programming.
Twining chose the name Al-Gon-Quian because he believed that was a possible Native American expression for "bow of a canoe." Twining also borrowed several Indian names for the camper groups. He divided the campers into groups by age, grade, height and weight. Throughout the years, the tribes within the camp included the Ottawa, Chippewa, Cree, Ojibwa, Miami, Nipissing and Mississauga. One common element that joins these native tribes together is that they were a part of the Algonquian linguistic family and spoke Algonquian when together. Al-Gon-Quian is still the universal language for the children who spend their summers with us.
In 1925, Mr. Twining opened camp for its first season. Sessions lasted 8 weeks, and boys came from all over Michigan and surrounding states. Prominent families from of the Ann Arbor community and the Midwest sent their sons to Camp Al-Gon-Quian. A brief list includes the Proctor & Gamble sons of Cincinnati, the Wrigleys of Chicago, the Strohs of Detroit and Grosse Pointe, and the children of noteworthy University of Michigan figures Alvin Bentley, C.S. Mott and G. Mennen Williams. Prominent members of the university community that served as staff members include Bennie Oosterbaan, Dr. Roger Howell, Roscoe Bonisteel, E. Blythe Stason and James B. Edmonson.
In addition to providing a fun outdoor experience for campers, Camp Al-Gon-Quian aimed to improve the character of young men. In 1932, the aims of camp were to develop strength of character, a purpose in life, a clear moral character, self-reliance and the ability to achieve. This was accomplished through two months of camaraderie and living in the great outdoors away from the stresses of city life. Campers often took an overnight train up north from Chicago or Detroit, spending their entire summers on Burt Lake.
Twining was well-recognized in the camping community and actively involved with the American Camp Association, of which he was the first national president in 1935. He was the director of Al-Gon-Quian for 42 years until his retirement in 1967, when he sold camp to the Ann Arbor YMCA.
The Camp Al-Gon-Quian records provide documentation of the campers and staff of this summer camp for boys in northern Michigan beginning in 1925 and continuing to 1967. The files provide personal information about campers and staff. The reords are arrange in X series, Camper Files, Staff / Counselor Files and Admininstrative Files.
Subjects:
Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.)
- Campers files 1925-1967
  The Campers files date from 1925 to 1967 is arranged into two sub-series: Chronological and Alphabetical. The bulk of these files are arranged by year and then alphabetically. A smaller sub-series is arranged alphabetically. These files were maintained separately by the camp administration. Each file includes correspondence, an information form filled out by the parent or guardian, a camper report sheet filled out by the camper's counselor, and a small photograph of the applicant. If a camper attended more than one year, the camp kept all of his records in the file dated when he first enrolled.
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1925
      [Restricted until January 1 2025 ]
      - Fletcher, Ralph (1925-1929) (Box 1)
      - Hunt, Morey (1925-1929)
    - 1926
      [Restricted until January 1 2026 ]
      - Ambrose, Dick (1926-1929) (Box 1)
      - Baldwin, William H. (includes Robert C.) (1926-1935)
      - Becker, Wilson
      - Belknap, Billy, Jr.
      - Brooks, Chuck, Jr. (1926-1927)
      - Bunn, George (1926-1927)
      - Bunn, Jacob, Jr.
      - Carson, Robert C. (1926-1927)
      - Churchill, Hobart (1926-1928)
      - Clark, David (1926-1928)
      - Cody, Fred (includes Burns) (1926-1928)
      - Culbertson, Jack (1926-1927)
      - Dare, Carl, Jr.
      - Dissette, Kester
      - Duffeck, Donald W. (includes Frank G.) (1926-1927)
      - Dyer, Fred (1926-1931)
      - Emmons, James (1926-1927)
      - English, John
      - Ford, Clinton
      - Forman, Dick (1926-1933)
      - Fuller, Dick (1926-1929)
      - Fulton, Pat (includes Jim) (1926-1927)
      - Gagnier, George, Jr. (includes Fred) (1926-1931)
      - Gardner, Raymond, Jr. (includes John) (1926-1938)
      - Graham, Wallace (1926-1927)
      - Grant, Charles M., Jr. (1926-1927)
      - Green, Mark
      - Higbie, Carleton M., Jr.
      - Holton, Philip (1926-1928)
      - Hoover, Gordon (1926-1928)
      - Howell, Robert (includes Roger & Roderick) (1926-1934)
      - Jensen, Walter (1926-1929 1935)
      - Krutzsch, Joe
      - Langford, Bob (1926-1932)
      - Leinbach, Billy (1926)
      - Lorimer, John (1926-1927)
      - Main, Robert
      - Matzen, Herman, Jr.
      - Maxson, Charles (1926-1929)
      - McClung, Garret (1926-1928)
      - McNeal, Harry (1926-1927)
      - Mead, John III (1926-1927)
      - Meddaugh, Burr
      - Moriarity, Eddie (1926-1927)
      - Mortenson, Bob
      - Munson, Jack (1926-1927)
      - Newman, Billy (1926-1931)
      - Northrop, Kimball (1926-1933)
      - O'Connor, A. Louis (includes Joseph) (1926-1927)
      - Paton, David
      - Pattengill, Keith P. (includes Victor R.) (1926-1931)
      - Patton, James W. (1926-1927)
      - Pittman, Lansing (1926-1933)
      - Ranney, George
      - Ratliff, Berry (1926-1934)
      - Ratterman, Fred (includes Pat & George) (1926-1935)
      - Richards, Pat (1926-1931) (Box 2)
      - Roach, James III
      - Robbins, Alton
      - Russell, Clayton
      - Sears, Bob (including Harold (1926-1927)
      - Skillman, Harry (1926-1927)
      - Smith, Franklin
      - St. John, Raymond, Jr.
      - Todd, Charles, Jr. (1926-1932)
      - Torbet, Bobby (1926-1927)
      - Torbet, Jack (1926-1930)
      - Viger, Dave
      - Ware, Frank
      - Wright, Charles III
      - Zimmermann, Dave
    - 1927
      [Restricted until January 1 2027 ]
      - Abbott, Waldo, Jr. (Box 2)
      - Bailey, Robert (1927-1928)
      - Baldwin, Douglas
      - Blake, John
      - Blakenburg, Bob
      - Burghardt, Gordon (1927-1929)
      - Butcher, Jack (1927-1929)
      - Cornelius, Russell M. (includes Phillip) (1927-1930)
      - Couzens, Jack
      - Crusoe, Jack (1927-1931)
      - Curtis, Malcolm (Sonny)
      - Davenport, Harbert, Jr.
      - Davies, John
      - Dean, Marshall (1927-1928)
      - Detwiler, Ralph (includes Tom)
      - Duffield, John
      - Eckert, Edwin, Jr.
      - Edwards, Harold, Jr. (1927-1930)
      - Fijux, Bart, Jr. (1927-1928)
      - Finn, John
      - Gage, Billy (1927-1928)
      - Gagnier, Fred (1927-1931) [empty-see George Gagnier]
      - Goss, Warren "Kelly" (1927-1929)
      - Hastings, Reeve (1927-1928)
      - Houlihan, Edward, Jr. (1927-1928)
      - Huntoon, Orrin, Jr. (1927-1929)
      - Jones, Charles, Jr. (1927-1929)
      - Keeney, John (1927-1928)
      - Kline, John (1927-1932)
      - Lord, Pater, (1927-1928)
      - McDougal, Leslie
      - Mills, Robert (includes Gordon) (1927-1930)
      - Newburgh, Henry
      - Oyler, Thomas (1927-1932)
      - Page, Billy
      - Patton, Chris
      - Pittman, Philip Mc Millan (1927-1931)
      - Ross, Bob, Jr. (1927-1930)
      - Sankey, Robert
      - Smith, Henry B., III (includes Frederick) (1927-1929)
      - Smith, Irving (1927-1928)
      - Smith, Tom C., Jr.
      - Spitzley, Bert (1927-1928)
      - Stephenson, William B. (includes Burnette) (1927-1931)
      - Stimson, Bob, Jr.
      - Turkington, Jack (Box 3)
      - Tyler, Theodore K. (1927-1929)
      - Varney, Murray
      - Wahlfeld, Willis
      - Welch, Kenneth C., Jr. (1927-1930)
      - Weller, Jack (includes Tom) (1927-1932)
      - Wickes, Ned (1928-1929)
      - Willeke, Leonard, Jr.
      - Woods, Sam (1927-1928)
    - 1928
      [Restricted until January 1 2028 ]
      - Adams, Edward (1928-1930) (Box 3)
      - Ames, Thomas W. (includes Knowlton L., Jr.) (1928-1929)
      - Anderson, Olds
      - Appel, Jack
      - Bennett, Thomas
      - Bigger, Harold (1928-1929)
      - Black, Alan
      - Bowen, John W. (includes Charles Clark, III) (1928-1931)
      - Brennan, Frederick (1928-1929)
      - Brown, Robert
      - Buhrman, Olds (includes Gerry) (1928-1931)
      - Burton, John
      - Campbell, Bob (1928-1930)
      - Chapin, James (1928-1929)
      - Christy, Arthur R., Jr. (includes Russ J.) (1928-1933)
      - Cooder, Billy
      - Crane, Matlock (includes Charles) (1928-1931)
      - Dale, James
      - Donaldson, John
      - Douglass, Fred (1928-1932)
      - Draper, Jesse O. (includes William D.) (1928-1929)
      - Eggleston, Neal
      - Flintermann, Donald
      - Flintermann, Edward
      - Fuller, Ned
      - Harrison, Orrin
      - Hutchinson, Billy (1928-1930)
      - Iben, Charles (1928-1930)
      - Jones, Buford (includes Herbert V., Jr.) (1928-1929)
      - Kendall, George
      - Matheny, Dixon (includes Rodman) (1928-1935)
      - McCallum, Philip
      - McLurg, John
      - McNulty, Joe
      - Middleton, Edward
      - Mills, Edwin (1928-1929)
      - Moore, Leon (1928-1929)
      - Mortenson, Alvin
      - Myers, Everett M. (includes Jack C.) (1928-1934)
      - Nusbaum, Howard (1928-1933)
      - Pierce, Sells (Box 4)
      - Powers, Harry
      - Reaser, Edward (1928-1929)
      - Rutledge, Jack B.
      - Saur, Donald F. (includes Edward) (1928-1931)
      - Schaffer, John
      - Scotten, Oren (1928-1929)
      - Seaverns, George, III (1928-1929)
      - Seeley, John
      - Shelton, Ralph (1928-1930)
      - Sheridan, Jack, Jr. (1928-1929)
      - Shields, James, III
      - Smith, Freddie [see Hank Smith, Box 2]
      - Sovereign, Jimmy
      - Symons, Billy
      - Thompson, Jack (1928-1932)
      - Tremble, Sidney
      - Tyler, Frank E. (1928-1930)
      - Uhl, Jack
      - White, Bob
      - Wilcox, John (1928-1933)
      - Winterbotham, John, III
      - Wright, William, Jr.
      - Zink, Jack (1928-1929)
    - 1929
      [Restricted until January 1 2029 ]
      - Arbon, Paul, Jr. (Box 4)
      - Baldwin, Bob [see Bill Baldwin-Box 1]
      - Baumgardner, Carlton M., Jr. (1929-1932)
      - Chapin, Carsten
      - Clark, William W., III
      - Christy, Art [see Russ Christy-Box 3]
      - Cummer, Robert North (1929-1931)
      - Davis, Billy (1929-1930)
      - Douglas, Philip A. (1929-1934)
      - Everett, James C. "Bud"
      - Florian, Paul A., III
      - Friedel, Joseph C. "Bud" (1929-1932)
      - Gerwe, Maurice C.
      - Hafford, Bradford (1929-1930)
      - Hixon, Stuart Mc D. (includes William L., III) (1929-1931)
      - Hoel, William B.
      - Huntington, George B. "Billy" (1929-1934)
      - Husted, Henry G. (includes Clark E.) (1929-1930)
      - Johnson, Sidney Hare
      - Keller, Paul (1929-1931)
      - Kemper, Bernard J.
      - Kenly, Perry H., Jr.
      - Kirby, Edward G., Jr. (1929-1930)
      - Lawson, Noble T., Jr. (1929-1930)
      - Lee, William M. (1929-1931)
      - Loud, Billy, Jr.
      - Low, Henri Mazyck Clarkson (1929-1930)
      - Macpherson, James G.
      - McKisson, Henry W. "Bud"
      - McLane, William J. "Billie"
      - Miller, John H. (includes Richard H.) (1929-1930)
      - Newlin, Donald E. (includes Richard F.) (1929-1931)
      - Palmer, Elliott P. (1929-1930)
      - Read, Charles R. (1929-1931)
      - Siemon, Bill [see Paul Siemon]
      - Siemon, Paul A. (includes William A.)
      - Spencer, Donald "Brud"
      - Spencer, William J. (1929-1931)
      - Spurgeon, William A. (1929-1930) (Box 5)
      - Stephenson, Bill [see also Bunny Stephenson-Box 2]
      - Stout, Albert H. "Bert"
      - Stroh, Edwin R., III (1929-1934)
      - Tenney, Perry G.
      - Unckrich, Robert H.
      - Van Winkle, Chuck [see Pete Van Winkle]
      - Van Winkle, William P. "Pete" (includes Charles K.)
      - Walbridge, Robert F. (1929-1933)
      - Walker, Wirt D., Jr. (1929-1931)
      - Walton, Thomas R. "Tim", Jr.
      - Welch, Billy [see Kenneth Welch-Box 3]
      - Weller, Jack [see Tom Weller-Box 3]
      - White, William F. (includes Bronson "Red") (1929-1931)
      - Winston, Charles Jr. (1929-1934)
      - Wolfe, Charles B.
    - 1930
      [Restricted until January 1 2030 ]
      - Adams, Dwight S. (1930-1932) (Box 5)
      - Austin, Joseph H. "Bud" Jr. (1930-1936)
      - Aymond, John P.
      - Bailey, Fred W., Jr. (1930-1931)
      - Beecher, W. Robert (1930-1932)
      - Bowen, Daniel W. (includes Mark G.) (1930-1932)
      - Brindle, James L.
      - Brown, Donn
      - Caldwell, Philip "Jack"
      - Carpenter, Jack
      - Coffman, Kenneth M. (includes Ray "Jack") (1930-1931)
      - Danson, Edward B. "Ned"
      - Foster, George B., Jr.
      - French, Daniel
      - Gatch, Nelson B., Jr.
      - Handeyside, Bruce (1930-1934)
      - Harris, William
      - Harrison, David
      - Hill, Stuart G.
      - Idema, Henry (1930-1931)
      - Idema, James M. (includes David G.) (1930-1931)
      - Jeffrey, J. Richard (1930-1932)
      - Johnston, Preston (includes Wickliffe)
      - Klein, Carl J.
      - Kleinheksel, John H.
      - Leckie, Andrew "Buck" (1930-1931)
      - Leckie, William H.
      - Lee, Alfred S. (1930-1934)
      - Matheny, Dixon [see Rod Matheny-Box 3]
      - McNabb, John M. "Micky" (includes Willis B.) (1930-1931)
      - McVay, Eugene J.
      - Mills, Laurence H. Jr.
      - Mills, Robert [see Gordon Mills-Box 2]
      - Moore, Louis M., Jr.
      - Morgan, Bill [see Richard J. "Dick" Morgan]
      - Morgan, Richard J. "Dick" (includes William B.) (1930-1931)
      - Mulkey, William F. (1930-1931)
      - Myers, Everett [see Jack Myers-Box 3]
      - North, Bill [see Harold North]
      - Oburn, William H., Jr.
      - Pulling, Bart (1930-1933)
      - Rank, James J. (1930-1936)
      - Reaves, William H., Jr.
      - Rider, Don K. (1930-1931)
      - Russell, Arthur L. (1930-1934)
      - Sandrock, Douglass (1930-1936)
      - Seymour, Paul H. (includes Jack) (1930-1932)
      - Smith, Maynard L., Jr. (includes Donald Martin) (1930-1934)
      - Stroh, Bernhard, IV
      - Wallace, Richard B. (1930-1931)
      - Williams, James Hazlewood (Jimmy)
      - Williams, Richard F. (1930-1933)
    - 1931
      [Restricted until January 1 2031 ]
      - Beal, James F. (Box 6)
      - Bell, Arthur R. (1931-1933)
      - Bragg, Edward
      - Buhrman, Olds (see Gerry Buhrman-Box 3)
      - Byrn, Donald (includes Robert)
      - Byrn, Robert W. (1931-1933)
      - Cherington, Paul W.
      - Coffman, Kenneth (see Jack Coffman-Box 5)
      - Doan, Herbert (see Aiden Doan)
      - Dolph, Charles L.
      - Duffy, James (1931-1932)
      - Dunhill, John S.
      - Edmunds, Charles (1931-1934)
      - Fletcher, John D., Jr.
      - Floyd, George
      - Gamble, David
      - Henry, Edwin B., Jr.
      - Idema, David G. (see also James Idema-Box 5)
      - Johnson, Charles B., Jr.
      - Kleinschmit, Clarence W. (includes Arthur W.) (1931-1933)
      - Langston, Douglas H.
      - McNabb, Willis B. (see also John McNabb-Box 5)
      - Newcomb, William W., Jr. (1931-1935)
      - O'Reilly, Eugene E. (1931-1932)
      - Osterhous, Douglas W. (1931-1932)
      - Paterson, Robert C.
      - Pew, Robert C.
      - Raymond, Donald G.
      - Richards, Philip (1931-1934)
      - Washburne, Hempstead (Teddy), III (1931-1933)
      - White, Ripley, Jr.
    - 1932
      [Restricted until January 1 2032 ]
      - Andrews, Ted (Box 6)
      - Bigles, Edward M. (1932-1935)
      - Caperton, John Hays, (1932-1933)
      - Carr, Richard (includes Robert) (1932-1933)
      - Collette, Richard
      - Conrad, Michael
      - Cooke, Wight
      - Coolidge, David Allen (1932-1935)
      - Cunningham, Dick (1932-1933)
      - Drackett, Bolton S. (1932-1933)
      - Ford, Charlie
      - Hansen, Frederick Christian
      - Harvey, Thomas C. (1932-1935)
      - Haynes, Lawrence S., Jr.
      - McKene, Don T., Jr. (1932-1933)
      - Ross, David (1932-1933)
      - Simmons, John William
      - Smith, Philip Brooks (1932-1934)
      - Whitehead, James Frazer (1932-1935)
      - Wilson, Jack Norman
    - 1933
      [Restricted until January 1 2033 ]
      - Berdan, Marshall Sheppey (1933-1934) (Box 6)
      - Bindley, Jos
      - Bradley, David Shedd
      - Brennan, Jack H. (includes Vincent M.)
      - Burhaus, Robert Nolan
      - Chesbrough, Robert Erwin (includes Frank) (1933-1935)
      - Christy, Earl Bradford
      - Cronin, Robert Paul
      - Dowse, Orrin King (1933-1936)
      - Good, John Clinton
      - Hayes, Webb Cook, III (1933-1934)
      - Helm, Geo W. (1933-1934)
      - Holabird, John Angur, Jr.
      - Johnson, Lambert (1933-1934)
      - Klingman, Teddy (Theo) (1933-1935)
      - MacKinnon, Charles Winship (1933-1934)
      - Paton, William Andrew (1933-1935)
      - Paul, Geo E., Jr.
      - Schorling, Otis (includes Clark) (1933-1935)
      - Smith, Donald M. (see also Maynard Smith-Box 5)
      - Sober, William Howard (1933-1936)
      - Spring, Dick (includes Warren) (1933-1936)
      - Stout, Richard Howard (1933-1934)
      - Torrence, Hugh Kirk
      - Trix, Herbert Phelps
      - Twining, Richard K. (1933-1935)
      - Wormer, David (1933-1936)
    - 1934
      [Restricted until January 1 2034 ]
      - Baker, Richard (1934-1935) (Box 7)
      - Barker, Don (1934-1936)
      - Beutel, Richard (1934-1935)
      - Binford, Tom W. (1934-1936)
      - Boutin, Russell (1934-1935)
      - Brock, Raymond
      - Clifford, O. Morton, Jr.
      - Cudlip, Jack M. (1934-1936)
      - Duncan, Vincent (1934-1935)
      - Emmons, William (1934-1935)
      - Fellows, David
      - Gilman, William (includes Frederick) (1934-1937)
      - Grubb, William A.
      - Huggins, William G. (1934-1938)
      - Henderson, Robert
      - Higbie, Peter (includes Bradley "Bud") (1934-1936)
      - Hooker, James
      - Hotchkiss, Andrew (1934-1936)
      - Huntington, Jay (1934-1935)
      - James, Thomas W., Jr. (1934-1935)
      - Johnson, Dan Lee
      - Keller, Richard (1934-1935)
      - Kimmerling, Don F.
      - Leckie, Robert
      - Lewis, Robert (1934-1936)
      - McCullough, Charles
      - McGiffert, Robert C. (1934-1936)
      - Mitchell, Granville (1934-1935)
      - Pettus, George (1934-1935)
      - Redfield, Bruce (1934-1935)
      - Rehmus, Charles
      - Richards, Fletcher, Jr. (Dick)
      - Robinson, Jefferson D., III (Jay) (1934-1935)
      - Saunders, Gordon (includes Billy) (1934-1937)
      - Sparks, Don
      - Storer, George B., III (1934-1936)
      - Thom, Milner
    - 1935
      - Baumgardner, Marvin (1935-1936) (Box 7)
      - Bootes, Edward (1935-1936)
      - Bowman, Bliss, Jr. (Bo) (1935-1936)
      - Chesbrough, Frank (see also Robert -- Box 6)
      - Estabrook, Arthur (1935-1936)
      - Frischkorn, Frank (1935-1936)
      - Gilchrist, Frank (includes Stewart)
      - Goldberg, James (includes Sol) (1935-1936)
      - Higgins, William (1935-1936)
      - Jones, Richard Hoster
      - Kleinschmit, Edmund W.
      - Mattern, Guinn (Tim) (1935-1936)
      - McDougal, Robert D., III (Bud) (1935-1936)
      - McKinney, Joseph M.
      - McMath, Francis
      - Morner, Richard (1935-1936)
      - Newberry, Handy (1935-1936)
      - Ratterman, George (see also Fred-Box 1)
      - Robertson, David (1935-1936)
      - Sauer, George Buechler
      - Schram, William (1935-1936)
      - Steubing, William (1935-1936)
      - Stone, Wade
      - Storer, James
      - Taylor, Brice (1935-1936) (deceased 11/29/1941)
      - Thompson, Bradley (1935-1936)
      - Twining, Herbert Harrison (Bud)
      - Vaile, Richard (1935-1936) (Box 8)
      - Van Dusen, Charles
      - Welker, John
      - Wheelock, John (1935-1936)
      - Whiting, Macauley (1935-1936)
      - Wiltse, Dean (includes John)
    - 1936
      [Restricted until January 1 2036 ]
      - Medical Records (Box 8)
      - Alison, Denis (Spike)
      - Alison, David (includes Tom)
      - Ballard, Tom
      - Bartemeier, John Albert
      - Bear, Tom
      - Bissell, John
      - Bonisteel, Roscoe O., Jr. (Bud)
      - Brown, Michael (Mike)
      - Brown, Tom
      - Carrel, George
      - Carruthers, Edward
      - Cottrell, Henry
      - Dillon, Robert
      - Dock, Robert
      - Edmonson, Don
      - Edwards, J. William
      - Edwards, Joseph
      - Emmert, Bruce
      - Finley, Robert
      - Fletcher, Charles
      - Gault, David
      - Geier, Eugene
      - Goldberg, Edward
      - Higbie, Charles
      - Hurlbut, Philip
      - Jeffrey, Steven
      - Lighthall, Billie
      - Limback, Paul
      - Lord, James
      - Lorenzen, Robert
      - MacGrellish, William H.
      - Moxley, Scott (includes David)
      - Paul, Jack
      - Platt, Henry
      - Reichhold, Dieter
      - Rice, Dan
      - Rorick, Marvin (1936-1937)
      - Spreng, Warren (see also Dick Spreng)
      - Stason, Blythe
      - Storer, Peter
      - Storrs, Philip (includes Al)
      - Thomas, Robert
      - Whiting, Henry
      - Wilson, Erwin
      - Wulsen, Tom
    - 1937
      [Restricted until January 1 2037 ]
      - Alvary, Leon, Jr. (Box 8)
      - Bement, Roberts Edwin, Jr.
      - Booth, Stephen (includes David)
      - Brunner, Toby
      - Buhrman, Peter
      - Carney, John E.
      - Carrick, C. William
      - Couzens, Frank, Jr.
      - Couzens, James
      - Duryea, F. Charles, Jr.
      - Fechheimer, Nate
      - Foley, William R.
      - Frey, John
      - Gardner, John
      - Gates, Dick
      - Geier, Otto
      - Griffith, William C., Jr.
      - Hildreth, Owen
      - Johnson, Frederick D.
      - Johnson, Harold
      - Low, Stephen
      - Mackenzie, Robert D., Jr.
      - Marshall, Dr. & Mrs. Mark
      - McIlwraith, John Gray (Box 9)
      - Murphy, John
      - Neave, Harold E., Jr. (Buzzie)
      - Pattengill, H. Richard
      - Saunders, Billie (see Gordon Saunders-Box 7)
      - Shaffer, Frederic S., Jr.
      - Sommer, Benjamin L. (includes Thomas P.)
      - Sperry, Donald D., Jr.
      - Terry, Paul B.
      - Wintringer, Robert L., Jr.
      - Woods, James Park, Jr.
      - Wuerfel, Robert D.
    - 1938
      [Restricted until January 1 2038 ]
      - Allen, Ross Lorraine, Jr. (Box 9)
      - Bopp, Andrew Richard
      - Cook, John Barth
      - Galster, John Frederic
      - Long, Samuel Spreng
      - Lyman, William H.
      - Peirsol, John Michael
      - Peirsol, Thomas Reardon
      - Rorick, Richard P.
      - Rorick, Robert Baker
      - Shuell, John M.
      - Simmons, Warren
      - Zeder, James Churchill
    - 1939
      [Restricted until January 1 2039 ]
      - Clifford, Churchill (includes Frederick) (Box 9)
      - Eden, Johnny
      - Garred, Thomas Arthur
      - Gorrell, Edgar S. (Peter)